Chase Harrington

Full Stack Developer

Well-qualified junior Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 6 months of related experience.

Education

2020-10 - Coding Boot Camp: Coding

Current

University Of Texas At Austin - Austin, TX

2012-06 - Undergraduate: General Studies

2013-01 Austin Community College - Austin, TX

2007-08 - High School Diploma

2011-06 Leander High School - Leander, TX

Work History

Current

2020-11

2015-05

2020-11 - Handyman

By His Hands LLC, Austin, TX

- Responded to maintenance requests in commercial and residential properties with great speed and efficiency.
- Prepared for new painting by removing previous materials with seam-cleaning, sandblasting, scraping and sanding.

2015-06 - Team Lead

Mosquito Control Systems, Austin, TX

- Installed between 2-3 systems per day with approximately 3000 completed installations.
- Prepared detailed reports on updates to project specifications, progress, identified conflicts and team activities.
- Set up and calibrated machinery to meet specific production requirements and meet desired tolerances.
- Established open and professional relationships with team members which helped resolve issues and conflicts quickly.

2014-08 - Call Center Representative

IEnergizer, Austin, TX

- Helped customers who had issues in-game via email or phone calls.
- Helped test the game before release for bugs and other issues.

2013-07 - Associate

2014-07 Walmart, Austin, TX

2012-06 - Sales Associate

2013-07 Tractor Supply, Austin, TX

Contact

Address

Austin, TX, 78758

Phone

(512) 961-9228

E-mail

acechaseharrington@gmail.com

Skills

Project Management



JavaScript programming



CSS proficiency



HTML expertise



Languages

Spanish

Japanese



